[ projector clicking ]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
[ intense music ]
Darkness , I charge you with this sign
mother in the night are mine .
I teach you the mystery of rebirth
work my mysteries in Earth .
Hear my ears and speak with my tongue .
Drawn to the heart and lip
five points to this fellowship .
I bring you ecstasy and rebirth .
Be with my things living on my own .
From me they come and to me they go .
I invoke you and call upon you
brought by seed and Earth .
Hear me with my ears and speak with my tongue .
- I invite you to come . - I invite you to come .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ school bell ringing ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ instrumental music ]
Get in , psycho .
[ chuckles ]
What ?
What the fu ..
You 're fuckin ' weird , dude .
[ cutlery clanking ]
[ sighs ]
[ instrumental music ]
[ music continues ]
[ chuckles ]
[ Mrs. Reyes sobbing ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
- Mom ? - Wait a second .
Honey , I said give me a second .
I just wanted to see if you were okay .
[ sniffles ]
[ heavy breathing ]
Where are you going on a school night ?
I 'm going to that book signing , remember ?
I told you .
Do whatever you want . I don 't care .
[ sniffling ]
Okay .
[ indistinct chatter ]
You get one of those tattooed on you .
Bad ass motherfucker .
- Hi . - Hi .
It 's an amazing book .
Thank you .
I find it really fascinating
because the writing is so good
and you take the subject seriously .
Thank you .
But I just wish that maybe you could write
a little bit more about rituals . Um ..
I think you 've got enough of them in there . No ?
Just , careful what you believe in .
Alright ?
Yeah .
- What 's your name ? - Leah .
Leah , that 's a lovely name .
- Thanks for coming . - Yeah , thanks .
♪ Now words fill me with power ♪
♪ Ask me why alone ♪ ♪
I love this part , about evil .
" I don 't think the devil 's role is to create evil ,
but rather to expose the evil in the hearts of men
by challenging their loyalty to God . "
Fuck , that 's cool .
I don 't care if this guy looks like my dad .
He 's still fuckin ' cool .
- Here . - Thanks .
Do you think our parents will always be our parents ?
What the hell does that mean ?
Like , I mean , like
we 're supposed to look up to them
but they 're really just fuckin ' people. right ?
Like walking in on them takin ' a shit ?
No . Like ..
[ laughter ]
I mean , like , they 're just people
and they fuck up and they make mistakes
and really they 're just fuckin ' people .
It 's weird .
[ instrumental music ]
[ Leah laughing ]
♪ A bird laid out at the blue moon ♪
♪ And the moon will care that the song singing ♪
♪ Won 't you care if it 's the end ? ♪
♪ Without the moon .. ♪
[ chuckles ]
Stop .
♪ Without your princes ♪
♪ The dancing really turned ♪
Okay .
- Okay . - Yeah . Okay , bye .
♪ The prince has .. ♪
♪ He really gave me some loving ♪
[ Aaron groans ]
Fuck .
[ engine revving ]
♪ You can 't erase the feeling ♪
♪ You know who knows the fantasy ♪
♪ Will take you to the eastern cloud ♪
♪ A gift for you unto the .. ♪
♪ Hey heh ♪ ♪
[ door closes ]
What 's wrong ?
You tell me .
Leah ? Leah !
Leah , get downstairs .
So , are you gonna tell me
that the book signing just ended
and you 're home right after like a good girl , huh ?
No .
I called the library
and I know what time it ended , so ..
So ?
So , I 'm tired of you lying to my face .
[ sighs ] I 'm trying to do the best I can , okay ?
I 'm havin ' a really hard time here
I need you on my side .
Well , you 're all over the place .
What is that supposed to mean ?
It means I don 't even know
who I 'm coming home to anymore .
[ sighs ]
Leah ..
... I just can 't do it here anymore , okay ?
I 'm trying , but I feel like I can 't breathe .
This place feels like your father 's funeral
every fucking day .
- I have to move on . - What ?
I didn 't wanna say anything in case
I changed my mind , but I signed a lease
on a place up north from here .
I 'm selling this house .
Honey , I need a fresh start
please understand .
We 're moving ?
Yes .
When ?
By the end of the month .
Oh , fu ..
[ breathing heavily ]
Fuck . Fuck .
[ death metal music ]
♪ Wolves bad dreams ♪
♪ Became nightmares of day ♪
♪ What do you bad disgust ? ♪
♪ A song a song ♪
♪ Domestic violence ♪
♪ Summoning victory rape ♪
♪ Violence violence ♪
♪ Reserve reserve ♪
♪ Abuse abuse ♪
♪ Domestic violence ♪
♪ Reserve result ♪
[ death metal music on earphones ]
[ instrumental music ]
[ inhales ]
[ sighs ]
You 're making pancakes ?
Sure , why not ?
Sit , sit .
Okay .
I 'm gonna be late for work , so enjoy .
Mwah !
Oh , I , um , I need to go to the new place today .
I want you to come with me .
I 'll pick you up after school . Okay ?
Leah ?
Yeah , okay .
[ sighs ]
[ door closes ]
[ door creaks open ]
[ sighing ]
- Are you serious ? - Yeah .
That 's fucking bullshit , just like that ?
Yeah , I don 't know what to do about it .
She 's taking me out there tonight .
I 'm sure I 'm gonna fucking hate it .
Here .
No , I shouldn 't , um , she 's picking me up soon .
That 's fucking bullshit .
[ instrumental music ]
[ music continues ]
[ sighs ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ intense music ]
Leah ?
Coming .
[ scoffs ]
[ Leah grunting ]
[ instrumental music ]
[ engine revving ]
So , what are you gonna do about work ?
Everything I do from the office
I can do from home .
And maybe I 'll get a little hobby job
on the weekends .
We can do it together , that could be fun .
I spend the weekends with my friends .
Well , you 'll make new friends at school .
Okay . We should talk about that .
I was thinking I can transfer you
after the holidays .
Does that sound good ?
- No . - No ?
No .
I don 't wanna change schools , Mom .
Why don 't you just let me get my license ?
I can drive myself down .
When you can afford your own car
and learn to drive , absolutely .
Well , when are you gonna let me do that ?
It 's like your way of controlling me .
I really don 't wanna fight with you today .
Would you be happy finishing the school year
and then transfer next year ?
I will drive you in the morning
pick you up after school .
Take it or leave it .
[ instrumental music ]
You have everything ?
- Are you sure ? - Yeah .
- Lunch ? Okay . - Yup .
I 'll be right here after school , okay ?
Okay .
[ music continues ]
[ Leah chuckles ]
- Oh . Fuck . - What ?
My mom 's waiting for me .
Well , we 'll see you this weekend , right ?
We 're going to that , like , stupid carnival thing .
No , I have to be up north with her .
Shit , that 's too bad .
Okay . Cool , see you later .
See ya .
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ sighs ]
Fuck .
Hey , kiddo , how was your day ?
Great .
[ engine revving ]
And you shouldn 't call me that either .
Well , that 's how you 're acting .
Hey ! Get down here , right now !
What ?
You know , you better start respecting me or ...
Or what , you 're gonna uproot my life ?
God , you are acting like such a brat !
Oh , how else am I supposed to act , Mom ?
You know , I am driving over two fuckin ' hours a day
so you can be with your stupid friends
- and that is not enough for you ! - Don 't call them stupid .
- Come here ! Come here ! - What ?
Give me your hand . Give me your hand .
- Fuckin ' don 't touch me . - Give me your hand .
What is this ? A pentagram . Oh !
You wanna be a Manson chick or something .
It 's ridiculous .
Ever since your father died
you 've been into that occult crap .
It makes me feel better !
- And my friends ... - Your friends ?
Your friends are losers , Leah ,
like you 're becoming .
I give up . I give up .
Oh , you give up ?
Moving on is impossible with you .
Every time I look at you , I see your father 's face .
God , I wish I could just wipe it off .
[ sighs ]
[ sobbing ]
[ intense music ]
Fuck . Fuck . Fuck .
[ sobbing ]
[ screams ]
I wish you were dead !
[ sobbing ]
[ intense music ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ sighs ]
[ laptop keys clacking ]
[ intense music ]
[ thudding ]
Darkness , I charge you with this sign
mother in the night are mine .
I teach you the mysteries of rebirth .
... upon you brought by ... seeds .
Hear with my ears and speak with my tongue .
I invite you to come .
Drawn by the heart and the head ..
Five points to this fellowship .
I bring you ecstasy and rebirth ..
From me they come and to me they go .
... mother in the night are mine .
Drawn to the heart and hip
I spin my mysteries in mirth .
Darkness , I charge you with this sign
mother in the night are mine .
I teach you the mysteries of rebirth
work my mysteries in mirth .
Drawn to the heart and lip
five points to this fellowship
I bring you ecstasy and rebirth
all things living on my own .
From me they come and to me they go .
I teach all things living on my own .
Hear with my ears and speak with my tongue .
I charge you with this sign
mother in the night are mine .
Drawn by the heart ..
Darkness , I charge you with this sign ..
Pyewacket .
Darkness , I charge you with this sign
mother in the night are mine .
I teach you the mystery of rebirth
work my mysteries in night .
Pyewacket .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ sobbing ]
I call upon you , brought by leaves and seeds .
Hear with my ears and speak with my tongue .
I invite you to come .
Pyewacket .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ thudding ]
[ intense music ]
[ music continues ]
[ grunts softly ]
[ panting ]
[ crow cawing ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ door opens ]
[ intense music ]
[ knock on door ]
You okay ?
[ panting ]
Yeah , I 'm fine . Just gimme a second .
[ music continues ]
- Ah ! - Oh , my God , honey .
Let me see .
Honey , what happened ?
We need to clean this .
[ whispering ] I know , I know .
[ breathing heavily ]
Okay .
[ sighs ]
Oh .
Alright .
Okay , hold this .
You can tell me ..
... if you ..
No , I.. It was an accident .
Where did you go ?
I just ..
Leah .
Leah , I am so sorry .
I should have never said that .
Honey , please forgive me .
Oh , God .
[ sighs ]
[ stairs creaking ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ intense music ]
Oh , my God , this is so cute .
Look .. Boo !
[ chuckles ]
Ah , we ... we saw this from the street .
- It is the cutest store . - Oh , thank you .
And I was wondering ..
D ... do you have an application
because I would really love
to work here on the weekends .
I think it would be so much fun .
- Alright . - Wow .
Okay , uh , you know what ..
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ intense music ]
[ music continues ]
[ sighs ]
Such a cute store .
I think it would be fun to work there on the weekends .
You alright ?
Yeah , let 's go get some lunch .
Sounds good .
[ gasps ] Mom !
[ screaming ]
[ tires screeching ]
[ panting ]
You okay ?
[ car alarm beeping ]
[ sighs ]
Not a scratch .
He said we were lucky .
[ intense music ]
I can 't believe how close that was .
[ sniffles ]
Did you know
that your father drove 13 hours straight
so he could lay eyes on you
as soon as you were born ?
He never told me that .
Oh , yeah .
He was away on a job .
He couldn 't afford a flight .
I told him it was okay .
I mean , I understood if he couldn 't make it .
But , you know your dad .
He rented this car anyway
and he drove straight through .
And the best part is
he did make it .
He rushed into the delivery room .
I mean , I barely remember , but ..
... I 've never seen him so excited .
And he thanked me
every single night for a year after that .
For what ?
You .
He said you were the best thing
that ever happened to him .
I know I 've been hard on you .
God , I 'm so sorry .
[ sighs ]
[ thudding ]
[ gasps ]
[ intense music ]
[ thudding ]
[ thudding continues ]
[ music continues ]
[ panting ]
[ thudding ]
Mom . Mom . Mom .
There 's someone in the house .
[ sighs ]
Leah , I don 't hear anything .
I swear there 's someone up there .
Okay .
Nothing .
Are you ... are you sure ?
No . See for yourself .
[ sighs ] Go on .
So , let 's have a break , when we come back
uh , we will answer questions .
I 'm sure you all have many as we do
as we got into today
which is absolutely fascinating .
[ intense music ]
[ sighs ]
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ intense music ]
[ music continues ]
[ trees creaking ]
[ intense music ]
[ leaves rustling ]
[ gasps ]
[ panting ]
Oh , fuck . Oh , God .
[ water sloshing ]
- Bullshit . - Why would I make that up ?
' Cause you 're nuts . I don 't know .
- Rob ... - No , it happened .
It 's happening . It 's real .
It 's fucking real .
I can 't believe you wanted to kill
your own mother .
That 's the scary part .
I mean , why ?
God , I would never do that .
I regret it , okay ?
And don 't be such a fucking hypocrite , Rob .
You do rituals all the time to try and get girls
and they never fucking work .
Yeah , but that 's not black-craft shit .
You want to kill your own fucking mother !
I 'm just sayin ' , if it worked
then maybe you deserve it .
Fuck you .
Fuck you , too .
- Leah . - Lee .
Leah . Come on , sit down .
[ sobbing ]
Fuck .
Listen , Leah , we 're here , okay ?
We ... we wanna help .
Why did you ..
Hm . Alright .
But what do you wanna do about it ?
I don 't wanna go back .
I can 't go back .
- Okay . - I 'll go .
I think it 's cool .
And I wanna see some weird shit .
We can , like , get it on camera or something .
[ foot tapping ]
What do you say ? Can I ?
Can I come up tonight and , like , stay over ?
Um , what about your parents ?
They don 't give a shit what I do .
It 's a waste of time .
She 's just looking for attention .
Well , we 're gonna find out while you sit at home
and jerk off tonight .
Fuck you .
[ chuckles ]
Yeah .
[ engine revving ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
Hey , mom , is it cool if Janice sleeps over tonight ?
- Oh , hey , Janice . - Hi .
Did you check with your parents ?
Yeah , they said it was cool .
And I 'd really like to come up , if that 's okay .
Sure . Of course , let 's go .
Sick .
[ Janice sighs ]
Fuck , man . This is brutal .
[ clattering ]
Aw . I love this .
Thank you , girls .
Thanks so much for dinner . It was really good .
Oh , you 're too kind .
Alright .
Okay , I 'm off to my room to get some work done .
You girls gonna be alright ?
- Yup . - Oh , Janice .
There 's a , a pillow and a blanket
on the couch for you .
Okay , that 's great . Thanks .
Um , thanks again for letting me stay .
Alright . Goodnight .
Night .
" Thank you , thank you . Yes , thank you . "
Shut up . Get back to work .
You have lots of dishes to do .
I 'm timing you , you take nine million years .
If you get this shit on my leather jacket , I will kill you .
[ chuckles ]
What ?
I 'm just happy you 're here .
Yeah , man .
Are you gonna put up posters or something in here ?
It 's so ... weird .
Uh , not yet .
Okay , what are we doing ?
[ chuckles ]
Get your phone out .
Okay .
Okay , it was .. Are you recording ?
Yeah . Wait , hold . There .
It was just up here
and it was making a ton of noise
so , let 's just ..
[ whispering ] You just wanna wait ?
Yeah , just give it a minute .
Or should we , like , summon it
like , call its name ?
[ laughing ]
Totally rando , but I would pick Billy Corgan
over , like , any guy .
Hands down , seriously .
♪ And my heart ♪
♪ Still loves you ♪ ♪
Leah , don 't worry . I believe you .
I wouldn 't be here if I didn 't .
Maybe I 'm nuts like Rob said .
Urgh ! Fuck Rob .
He 's just jealous ' cause he likes you
and he knows you 're into Aaron .
What ? No , I 'm not .
Oh , my God . You two , it 's too fucking obvious .
Uhh ..
Why , did he say something ?
[ chuckles ]
Wondering .
Um , I will tell you
if you smoke this joint with me .
Like , your mom moved , like , most of the shit
but , like , all the fuckin ' owls .
- Dude , they 're everywhere . - Yeah , I don 't get it .
She put one in your fucking room .
So she says , she 's just , like , watching me .
- It 's fucked up . - That shit creeps me out .
Not much creeps me out , but that shit does .
I don 't know what it is about owls .
I don 't know .
They can turn their heads all the way around .
- And their eyes are huge . - Where did you do it , by the way ?
Over there in the woods .
Well , show me , come on . Let 's go .
No . It 's way too dark out .
We 'll use the fucking flashlight on my phone .
It 's not that far , right ?
What 's the point ?
Because I want to see it . That 's why I came up .
Come on , please ?
Where are we going ?
- This way ? - Yeah .
It 's just a little further .
- Watch out . - Huh .
[ gasp ]
[ exhales ]
You see it ? Right up ahead .
- Oh , yeah . That ? - Yeah .
It 's perfect .
[ indistinct chatter ]
- This , right ? - Yeah , right here .
- Ah .. - Right here .
Yeah , you 're right .
It is really creepy out here .
Yeah .
[ trees creaking ]
It 's really scary .
Heh .
[ trees creaking ]
What are you doing ?
Janice , stop that .
Hey , stop that .
[ sighs ] Good .
[ Leah sighs ]
Janice ?
Janice , what are you doing ? Stop .
Hey , where are you going ?
Janice !
Come back !
[ sighs ]
Janice ?
[ door creaking ]
[ sighs ] Janice !
Janice , this isn 't funny anymore .
[ panting ]
My God .
You 're an asshole ! I 'm leaving .
Wait ! Leah , wait !
I 'm fucking around . You 're so funny .
[ Janice chuckling ]
You are such a loser .
- What ? - I was just fucking around .
It isn 't funny . I 'm stoned .
I know , I 'm sorry .
Well , okay , I think I 'm just gonna go to bed .
- I 'm tired . - Okay .
- I love you . - I love you , too .
Hey , I 'm , I 'm sorry . I was just , like , fucking around .
Hm . No , that 's fine .
I 'll ... see you in the morning .
- Goodnight . - Goodnight .
[ intense music ]
[ music continues ]
[ sighs ]
Honey ?
Where 's Janice ?
It 's so strange .
[ scoffs ]
Janice ?
Leah ?
What is it ?
My car .
[ door opens ]
Hey , Janice , are you okay ?
Janice , unlock the door .
Janice , what 's going on ?
[ whimpering ]
- Please open the door . - Hey .
- Take me home . - What ?
- Please , please . - Janice .
- Take me home ! - Janice !
I just wanna go home !
You need to open the door .
- Please . - Please just unlock the door .
[ Janice sobbing ]
I 'll get the keys .
Okay .
[ sobbing ]
Janice ?
Janice , what 's wrong ? What happened ?
[ Janice sobbing ]
I 'll , I 'll make you something to eat .
You 'll feel better .
No ! I 'm not , I 'm not going back inside that house !
- Hey ... - Don 't touch me !
[ Janice sobbing ]
Okay , let 's go .
Okay , take out your books
and pick up where we left off .
Chapter two , part two .
From the paragraph that starts with
" Evening was coming on
when he reached home . "
Finish the chapter and write a paragraph , uh ..
[ cell phone chimes ]
[ engine revving ]
Oh , okay .
No , I really don 't know . It was the strangest thing .
I 'm worried about her .
Yes , please , keep me posted . Thank you .
Janice hasn 't left her bedroom .
Any luck ?
I texted her all day , and nothing .
[ sighs ] She really scared me .
Do you know if she 's going through something ?
No , I don 't think so .
I got a call from the gift shop
and they want me to come in tomorrow .
I really wanna do this . Please don 't get mad .
Why would I get mad ?
I won 't be able to pick you up from school tomorrow
so you 'll have to take the bus .
At first I thought no ,
but it 'll be good for you .
- What do you think ? - Okay .
- You 'll be okay alone ? - Mm-hmm .
[ dramatic music ]
[ sighs ]
[ keyboard keys clacking ]
[ laptop beeps ]
[ gasps ]
[ sighs ]
[ chuckles ]
[ keyboard keys clacking ]
[ door shuts ]
I was really fucking worried about you , man .
Like , are you okay ? You weren 't answering any of my texts .
Yeah , I 'm sorry .
Well , what about Janice ?
I haven 't seen her since she went up with you .
Look , I , I really gotta go .
I 'll just talk to you later .
Leah , if I did something , you 'd tell me , right ?
Yeah , I just really need to go right now , okay ?
I 'm sorry .
A dark spirit like Pyewacket
is very manipulative .
So am I right to assume that during the ritual
you believed in it as much as you believe
I 'm talking to you right now ?
- Yeah . - Okay .
Then we have to assume it 's here .
You need to think of it as a river .
Evil is simply waiting across on the other side
and you used yourself as a bridge
to bring them over to your side .
And once they fulfill the task you asked of them
they 'll start hurting the person they communicated with .
And that 's you , Leah .
With black magic , it 's thrown back .
It starts with you
and it will end in you .
To undo this , you need to perform
the exact , the exact same ritual
in the same place , but in reverse .
At every step , you ask for forgiveness .
Leah , this is very important .
You have to do this before it gets to your mother
or it 's too late .
Pyewacket can take many forms
so don 't trust your lying eyes .
[ dramatic music ]
[ door opens ]
[ crow cawing ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ panting ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ engine revving ]
Leah ?
Leah !
[ gasps ]
Hello ?
[ intense music ]
[ gasps ]
[ panting ]
Leah !
[ breathing heavily ]
Fuck .
911 . What is your emergency ?
[ sobbing ] My mom just died .
[ sobbing ]
What is your name ?
- I 'm ... I 'm Leah Reyes . - Okay .
- Everything 's gonna be okay . - Okay .
Can you just tell me where you are
and exactly what happened to your mother ?
I don 't know , I don 't , I don 't even know where I am .
I don 't know where I am and I don 't know what to do .
- Please help me . - Okay .
- Stay calm . - Leah !
Who 's that calling out , Leah ?
Can you put them on the phone ?
- I don 't know . - Leah !
Can you put her on the phone ?
Leah ? Are you still with me ?
[ panting ]
[ keypad beeping ]
Leah , it 's nice to hear from you .
- Aaron , please help . - What happened ?
Aaron , I can 't be here anymore . Please , come get me .
Okay , I can 't get the car until later when my parents leave .
No , please , I ... I need you right now .
I don 't know if I could drive that far .
[ panting ]
Aaron , just please come .
[ trees creaking ]
[ panting ]
[ cell phone buzzes ]
[ sobbing ]
[ gasping ]
Leah .
Come inside .
Close the door .
[ panting ]
Where were you ?
Where 'd you go ?
Out for a walk .
With that ?
What were you gonna do with it ?
I should put it away .
Leah ?
Just let me in .
[ door rattling ]
Just open the door .
Leah !
Come outta your room !
Right now !
[ pounding on door ]
[ witch growling ]
[ clattering ]
[ intense music ]
[ glass shattering ]
[ panting ]
[ pounding on door ]
No .
Oh . Damn !
[ witch growling ]
[ Leah gasps ]
[ growling ]
[ screaming ]
[ panting ]
Please . Please . Please .
[ sobbing ]
Please .
[ floorboard creaks ]
[ mumbles ]
Please . Please .
[ sobbing ]
Please . Please . Please .
Oh , plea .. Please .
Oh , my God , please , please .
[ sobbing ]
- Get away from me ! - Honey .
[ panting ]
- Get away ! - Honey ?
Let go of the knife .
Get away from me ! No !
No , I know who you really are .
I know who you really are !
Just get , get away from me !
Please , just give me the knife .
[ panting ]
No . No . No . No . No .
Don 't , don 't touch me !
[ panting ]
- It 's okay . - No .
- Honey . - No .
[ panting ]
Don 't . Don 't .
[ breathing heavily ]
Leah , what were you doing in the woods earlier ?
I was calling for you .
And why do you have a knife ?
What were you gonna do with it ?
I 'm gonna hang on to it tonight .
[ panting ]
[ intense music ]
[ music continues ]
[ panting ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ door opens ]
Hm ..
Honey , what is it ?
Honey ?
[ sighs ]
What 's that smell ?
[ breathing heavily ]
Leah ? What are you doing ?
Leah ?
Leah !
[ screaming ]
Oh , God ! Oh !
[ breathing heavily ]
[ Mrs. Reyes screaming ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ fire crackling ]
Leah !
Leah ?
Leah , wake up . Come on , wake up !
Leah ! Leah , come on , wake up !
Wake up !
Can you just tell me where you are
and exactly what happened to your mother ?
I don 't know . I don 't , I don 't even know where I am .
I don 't know where I am and I don 't know what to do .
- Please help me . - Okay .
- Stay calm . - Leah !
Who 's that calling out , Leah ?
Can you put them on the phone ?
- I don 't know . - Leah !
Can you put her on the phone ?
Leah ? Are you still with me ?
We didn 't find your mother 's body in the woods , Leah .
The only one we found was in your house
burned to ash .
Was that your mother ?
[ sobbing ]
Let 's try this again .
How did the fire start ?
Subtitles by explosiveskull
[ instrumental music ]
[ music continues ]